### Luyanda Shamase

Mobile & Web Developer

### Personal details



luyandashamase5@gmail.com



0788680553



18 Rippon Road, Durban, 4091



github.com/Luyanda078



linkedin. com/in/luyandashamase-583b29214

### **Technical Skills**

Node.js & React.js	••••
React Native	••••
JavaScripts	••••
HTML	••••
Tailwind CSS	••••
MongoDB	••••
Firebase	••••
GitHub	•••••
Microsoft Azure	••••

# Soft Skills

**Detail Oriented** 

**Excellent Problem Solver** 

Ability to analyze Technical Information

Team-Working

Interpersonal Skills

### **Profile**

A highly disciplined and skilled Information & Communications
Technology (ICT) candidate with a good academic background
and practical experience in Mobile and Web Development, Cloud
Computing, AND Scholarly Research.

Recently graduated with a Bachelor of ICT Honors.

# Experience

#### **Trainee - Mobile & Web Developer**

Jul 2024 - Present

mLab Southern Africa, Pietermaritzburg

- As a developer trainee, I collaborated on defining and developing mobile & web software requirements and digital solutions.
- My role includes learning application development, creating design documents, debugging, refactoring, and maintaining quality documentation.
- Participating in Scrum events, implementing and maintaining features, creating user guides, and emphasizing self-organization, planning, and timely task completion.

#### **CodeTribe Tribe Academy**

Apr 2024 - May 2024

mLab Southern Africa, Virtual BootCamp

- Web development bootcamp at the CodeTribe Academy hosted by MLab.
   Programme provided introduction to Web development, specifically focusing on HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Developed our own applications, deployed pushed and hosted all the tasks to GitHub accounts.

#### **Casual Laborer**

Sep 2017 - Jan 2021

Mr Price DC, Mpumalanga Township

 Performed stock receiving, stock taking, scanner stock auditing, scanner pallet building, and offloading and in-loading of stock during company peak seasons and holiday breaks.

# Certificates

**Microsoft Azure DevOps (AZ-400)** 

Present

Azure Administrator Associate (AZ-104)

Sep 2024

**Microsoft Azure Fundamentals (AZ-900)** 

Jul 2024

mLab Certificate of Participation Dev.

May 2024

# Education

#### **Bachelor of ICT Honors Degree**

Jan 2023 - Dec 2023

Durban University of Technology

South Africa - Durban

#### NQF8

 Applied Research in ICT; Analysed contemporary literature and establish a focused topic for my investigation. Synthesized and reported recent and relevant information in a cogent and coherent manner.

# Languages

**English** 



IsiZulu



- Applied META Analysis & Systematic Literature Review(SLR) for data collection and analysis techniques on my research study.
- Cloud Computing || Advanced Data Analytics || Advanced Cybersecurity || Advanced Software Development & Management || Global & Professional Practice

### **Advanced Dilploma in ICT**

Jan 2022 - Dec 2022

**Durban University of Technology** 

South Africa - Durban

#### NQF 7

- Programming Languages: Python
- Databases: MySQL
- Machine Intelligence || Research Skills || Software Development and Management
- Key focus areas; Data Structures || Basic Mathematics for Computing || Business Intelligent || Platform Base Development

### **Diploma in Information & Communications**

Jan 2018 - Dec 2021

**Technology: Applications Development** 

**Durban University of Technology** 

South Africa - Durban

#### NQF 6

- Programming Languages: C#(.NET)
- Database: MySQL
- Information Systems(IS) & Applications Development Projects 1 3(App. Dev)
- Key focus Areas; Object Oriented Programming (O.O.P) || Agile Methodology
   || System Design and Development || MVC || Databases || Operating Systems
   || Human Computer Interaction (HCI) & Mobile Computing

# References

#### Dlozi Mthethwa

Facilitator mLab Southern Africa, Johannesburg 0763509451 dlozi@mlab.co.za

Research Supervisor Subashnie Soobramoney

Durban University of Technology subashniem@dut.ac.za

### Mpumelelo Ndlovu

Iress, Johannesburg 0794949922